Guide to the Dept. of Music Sound Recordings, 1956 - 1990 UA.25.28.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2005-0060
  - Duke Composers Concert, April 19, 1980, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Duke Chapel Choir, Messiah, December 8, 1957, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - David Thomas Recital with R. Larry Todd, February 6, 1990, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Faculty Chamber Music Program, February 2, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Claudia Bloom Recital, April 5, 1982, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Meredith Marcellus Recital with Wayne Lail, April 2, 1976, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Little Symphony Orchestra, 1953, 1956 and undated, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - November 11, 1953 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - Raleigh Performance, October 28, [no year], 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - November 29, 1956 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Duke String Quartet, 1963, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - Duke String Quartet, February 16, 1963 (Box 19)
    - Duke String Quartet, April 6, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Bloom Sisters, November 9, 1986, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Claudia Erdberg Recital, April 1, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Barbara Lister-Sink Recital, November 13, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1975-1978, 4 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - November 1, 1975 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - October 29, 1977 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - October 21, 1978 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Giorgio Ciompi, Boaz Sharon Recital, January 21, 1978, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, Student Piano and Arias Concert, May 10, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1963, 1971 and undated, 5 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - October 8, 1971 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - December 17, 1963 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - Concert with Joseph Pepper, undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Duke Small Orchestra, 1963-1964, 5 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - February 22, 1964 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
      Includes members of the New York Woodwind Quintet and the New York Brass Quintet.
    - January 1963 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - October 18, 1964 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - February 22, 1964 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1976, 1979, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - November 19, 1976 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
    - March 21, 1979 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 19)
  - Warwick Lister, Barbara Lister-Sink Recital, January 12, 1976, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke Madrigal Singers, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Warwick Lister, Barbara Lister-Sink Recital, March 21, 1976, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke String Quartet, 1963-1964, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - February 15, 1964 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
    - April 6, 1963 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Julia Mueller, Ruth Friedberg, Frank Bennett Recital, January 8, 1965, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Stephen Robinson Recital, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - [Noye's Fludde], Duke Chapel, September 27, 1975, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke Madrigal Singers, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - John Hanks, Ruth Friedberg, American Art Songs, November 20, 1974, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - John Hanks, Ruth Friedberg, September 6, 1974, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke Concert Band, December 4, 1964, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - University of Michigan Symphony Band, April 28, 1963, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - University of Illinois Summer Orchestra, August 4, 1960, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - The Triangle Little Symphony, January 20, 1963, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - New York Philharmonic, Giannini Symphony No. 2, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke Symphony Pops, March 12, 1960, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - William Schuman Lecture, On Being An American Composer, January 8, 1962, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Vittorio Giannini lecture, March 19, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Duke Duo Recitals with Ruth Friedberg, Julia Mueller, February 1, 1964, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Frances Perry Recital, October 9, 1975, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 20)
  - Student Concerti, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Chapel Choir, Messiah, December 13, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Loren Withers recital, February 22, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Boaz Sharon recital, October 29, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Francis Perry recital, February 8, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Steve Kimbrough and Ruth Friedberg recording session, September 1975 (Box 21)
  - Bloom Sisters recital, November 9, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Hanks and Friedberg, "American Art Songs," May 6, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Katherine Posner recital, February 5, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Frances Redding and Wayne Lail, "Love Triangles in Opera," February 9, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Frances Redding recital, October 26, 1973 (Box 21)
  - John Duke Songs, November 5, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Betty Bullock recital, April 30, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Duke String Quartet, February 15, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Ciompi and Withers recital, November 14, 1964, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Mueller and Friedberg recital, October 23, 1962, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Raimi and Hawkins recital, October 18, 1975, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Performances of Satie by Jane Bathori and Darius Milhaud; Serge Koussevitsky and the Boston Symphony Orchestra performing Satie, undated, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, Academic Festival Orchestra, March 18, 1965, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Douglas Knight commencement sermon, 1976; News of Duke, undated, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 21)
  - Mary Lou Williams Trio, December 10, 1977, 2 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Hanks and Friedberg, Art Songs in America, undated, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Mueller, Continuing Education lectures, September-November 1977, 7 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Duke University Chorale, November 12, 1978, 2 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Steven Kimbrough, Opera Highlights and Songs, 1972-1973, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Duke-UNC faculty recital, Concert Music of Antonin Dvorak, December 1, 1982, 2 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Duke University Concert Band, 1963-1964
    - 1963 concerts, 2 audiocassettes (Box 21)
    - April 15, 1964 concert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
    - December 1964 concert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1964, 1965 and undated, 3 audiocassettes
    - Brahms concert, undated, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
    - March 18, 1965 concert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
    - March 22, 1964 concert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - African Sanctus, undated, 2 audiocassettes (Box 21)
  - Faculty Recitals, 1979-1982, 42 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 22)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1972-1978 and undated, 42 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 23)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1970-1989, 36 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 24)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1970-1989, 21 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 25)
  - Woody Shaw with Duke Jazz Ensemble, 1985, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Evans Hanks Israeli Songs, 1981, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Joyce Peck, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Joyce Peck, 1981, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Duke Symphony, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Duke Collegium, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Joyce Peck, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Donna Coleman, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Collegium, undated, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 26)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Duke Musicum Collegium, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Student Recitals, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - George Taylor, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Randy Love, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Joyce Peck, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Fred Raimi, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - A. Ciompi, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Richard Luby, 1981, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Nelson Music Room, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 27)
  - Fred Raimi, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Claudia Bloom, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1981-1985, 6 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1980, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - DSO Chamber, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - DSO, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Duke Symphony, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Paul Jeffrey, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 28)
  - Jill Swisher with Duke Wind Symphony, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - DSO, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Jan Herliniger, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Stravinsky and Duke Students, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Warburg-Battersby, undated, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Unlabeled, undated, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Collegium, 1985, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Graduate Composer Concert, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 29)
  - Wind Symphony, 1990 and undated, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Collegium, 1981-1990, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Claudia Bloom, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Claudia / Madeline Bloom, 1990, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Berg Recital, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Fred Raimi, 1985, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Student Chamber Music, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Boaz Sharon, 1981, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - F. Raimi / J. Hawkins, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 30)
  - Loren Withers, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Randy Love, 1983-1985, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Jensen, Moses, Hawkins, 1984, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Claudia Bloom, 1986, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Rebecca Troxler, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Hanks and Friedberg, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Performance Practice Workshop, 1990, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - B. Berg and R. Love, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Bruce Berg / Jane Hawkins, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Robert Parkins, 1986, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 31)
  - Robert Parkins, 1981-1985, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Peter Marshall, 1981-1984, 3 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - David Arcus, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Composers Concert, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Donna Coleman, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1981-1985, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Jaffe Encounters, 1987, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 32)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1981-1986, 13 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 33)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1985, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Steven Bishop, undated, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Claudia Erdburg and Jane Hawkins, 1981, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - George Taylor, 1981, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Fletcher Residents, 1983-1984, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - DSO, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Wind Symphony, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Lost Eden, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Musicum Collegium, 1989, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)
  - Collegium Vocale, 1988, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 34)